Welcome in to another episode of Free
Agency Fridays here in the Big Bear AI
Command Center Studio. I'm your host
Brian Kobit Jr. here with my brother
Allp Pro Revo, a bachelor for only two
more days. A fiance only two more days,
brother. Congratulations, man.
>> Man, appreciate that, brother. Thank
you.
>> How dope was that signing that
extension, man, with everything you've
been through.
>> Oh, man. It's uh anytime, right, you get
to sign a line again, that's a blessing,
bro. like from where I started and where
I'm at now, like I seemed like a distant
afterthought back then, right? Like I
was just trying to make it,
>> you know? I was just trying I was
scratching and calling to just get in
the door. Um and now you fast forward to
where I'm at today on my third contract.
Like God is real and God is good because
uh there are very few people um that
have, you know, been fortunate enough to
make it through those storms like that.
And uh yeah, man. just ain't quit. I'm
thankful.
>> And thank goodness you didn't quit, man.
Because you have been through so much,
bro. Pack the squad, cut, uncut, signed,
all pro injuries, man. What a journey
you've had when you sit here today and
maybe it hasn't hit you yet because, you
know, you're running your rounds, doing
your your car wash, media interviews,
man.
>> What comes to mind when you sit and
reflect on the journey that has been
your NFL career?
>> Oh, man. It's uh
you know it's funny because
I always knew I remember when I went
undrafted I remember going home and I
was crying. I was boohoo crying because
I felt like that moment was taken from
me that I work for so much. But I
remember saying that my story was going
to be just a little bit different than
everybody else's. God uses all of us
differently. Some of us are used as
tools to show other people that it's
possible.
>> I happen to be one of those instruments.
And uh so I had to embrace the suck as a
coach I know used to say. Um you got to
embrace the storm. You gotta go through
it and you're not just going through it
for you because coming out on the other
side of it, there's been so many other
people that have been like, "Hey bro,
like what you went through helped me go
through this or what you went through
helped me push through this aspect of
life." Um, and so yeah, bro, like to put
it as simple as that, like my storm
wasn't just for me. It was for so many
other people to see that like you can
start here, but you don't have to end
there.
>> Like there's so much more for you out
>> You just got to keep fighting.
>> You got to keep putting one foot after
the next and you got to keep picking
yourself up every time you get knocked
down
>> and take the lessons from it. That's it.
>> And it's a lot easier to say that on
this side of it, right? But I love these
conversations with y'all because there's
young kids that are going through it.
There's current players that are going
through all of these things. Man, how
did you weather your storm?
>> Um, I focused on me.
>> I prepared every day as if I was going
to play because in this business, right,
like those who are prepared play. That's
how it works.
>> Um, there is no, oh, well, he hasn't
played and nobody cares. I don't care.
Right. So I had to treat every day like
it was my game rep. Every practice rep
was my game rep. Um film study. I was
still watching film on opponent
opponents like the rest of the group
studying you know 12 14 hours whatever
it might be because
like that's how I'm training my mind and
my body right so I took each day as if I
was on active even when I wasn't. M
>> um
and I would say the second part of it
was like I embraced that I needed to
learn. I understood that I didn't have
all the answers. Um and that for me to
get to where I wanted to get first I had
to learn.
>> Um and I had to sit back and be able to
watch the game from a different lens,
right?
>> Learn the game from a different lens. So
when the opportunity came, I would be
prepared for it. So there was different
aspects of you know that that came with
it. Um but uh yeah man, like when you in
a fire and the fire hot, it's a lot
easier or it's a lot tougher to, you
know, to get up every day when when all
the chips is stacked against you,
>> man.
>> But uh you know, at the end of that
fire, right, like when that fire
settles, like there is new life on the
other side of it, you know, and so like
you know, me believing in God and in the
word, right? Fire cleanses.
Hey bro, you just got to go through it.
>> Man, God is good, man. God is good. And
again, it's easier said than done. I
think back to a few years ago, you
suffer an injury and you walk in this
building. My my office was still over
here. You come to me say, "Hey man, I'm
headed home. I got to go rehab."
>> And you know that I will say that was
probably one of my more sad days in the
office just because of knowing the kind
of work you put in, knowing what that
meant for you to say bye like that. In
that moment, man, did you see today
coming? Did you see you being able to be
not only a special teams maven, not only
a guy that gets an extension, but a guy
that is a true part of the future of the
success of this defense
>> to be honest with you.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. And I say yes because
man, I had already been seasoned, bro.
>> I had already been through every season
of life, right? Like I had lost my mom
here and I went through that
>> and then I've been cut so many times
here and I weathered that and then I got
hurt. It's like yeah man like small
thing.
>> Let's go. All right. What's it what's
the verdict? All right. Was it the
surgery? All right. This let's get it.
>> That's how I had that's how you I mean I
have just life has life for me. You know
what I'm saying? Just like it has for
everybody. And so I had been through
those seasons that had prepped me for
that season. And that season was no
different than that. It's trials, right?
It's tribulations, right? It's
everybody's going through it. And I
guarantee somebody had it probably worse
than I did. Um and so yeah, man, the
approach was just no excuses. You So
what? Now what? Like we we here and the
the condition and the situation ain't
changing it. We got to go through it.
But it was it was tough, man. like those
first few days after surgery, right?
Like it's no sleep, you crying, you you
feeling sorry for yourself, you all
those human emotions, you know, like
that make it real of like being in that
moment, but um
you know, the
>> the the the part of me that I'm been
known for kicked in and quick and was
like, "All right, like come on." Like,
listen, bro, you got knocked down for a
reason. Let's find the win in this
somehow. Let's find the good in this
somehow so we can apply that to the work
that needs to be done going forward. So
yeah,
>> and that's why I wanted to start there
because your story is a true testament
of just getting through it. Self-belief
because all that self-belief, all that
preparation that you said you had,
>> it came to fruition last season, right?
Again, special teams guy,
>> not a real role on this defense or at
least not a real defined role yet.
>> Guys get injured. Now it's time for a
whole pro revo to be up on that field at
the defense. And then all season long we
see you throwing your body around. You
taking people out. You making hard hits.
You're making every moment count for
those opportunities you were given. Man,
what went right for Jeremy Reeds last
year?
>> Um
I mean realistically like you know
that's the nature of the game, right?
People go down, people get hurt. It
happens every year on every team.
>> Um and it's next man up. Like I said,
nobody cares who's going in. Nobody
cares if it's a special teams guy, if
it's a practice squad guy. When the
people turn on the TV or when the people
get in the stadium, they expect to see a
certain type of product.
>> They're paying their hard earned money
to come see a good product of the team
that they grew up either cheering for or
became fans of or whatever it may be.
So, that's not only like my opportunity
is not only for just me, right? I'm
getting a chance to go play defense and
do things that like I always dreamed of
as a kid. But it's for these people that
also, you know, give their time and
money to come watch us, right? Without
them, there is no league. There is no
business. It all runs through them. So
like I'm just paying back the people
that spend so much time and effort to
like support us and support me, you
know?
>> Um
>> but yeah, that season was uh it was it
was gratitude, man. like you know you
just don't know when it the opportunity
comes. Like I prayed for that years and
years ago.
>> I asked God for that years and years
ago. No different than like going to the
Pro Bowl. I told people in 2019 I was
going to go to the Pro Bowl in an
interview back home.
>> You fast forward like you know 2022 or
what I think that it's when it happens.
So, like you just don't know when God is
preparing the plate for you
>> and you just got to just stay forward.
Like he he's going to test you. You got
to have the test before the testimony. I
always say that. So, you got to weather
it. Like you got to go through it
because he's going to see just how bad
you want it and just how patient enough
you're going to be with him to get it.
And if he if you're prepared for that
blessing, like that's the thing. Like
you're not going to get a blessing that
you're not prepared for at all. So,
yeah, man. That's
>> that's it. And you're a true testament
of God's timing is everything. There's a
a divinity in God's timing. And we look
at that today because you sign this
contract,
>> get you a little extra money in your
pocket, and then two days from now, my
brother,
>> you will be getting married to the love
of your life.
>> The beautiful woman that we've seen
supporting you through all these games,
the young lady who we saw you propose to
right at Northwest Stadium, right on
that field. Man, we feel like we're a
part of your family. And we can sit and
talk football and the Ronte Jones system
and all that, man. But I want to talk
about that aspect, brother, because what
a blessing that is, man. This timing of
everything, bro. This is it surreal for
you right now.
>> Yeah, man. Like,
>> you guys are a part of my family. Like,
>> I've been through life here. I became I
said this earlier, I became a man here.
Like, life knocked me down and I got
back up and life knocked me down. I got
back up and then life rewarded me and
then, you know, I got knocked down
again. And so like I went through real
stuff here and like I experienced so
much here with everybody here that like
you guys are a part of my family. That's
why it was so cool to propose after that
game against the Falcons to go to the
playoffs, right? Because I didn't want
that moment to just be about me, right?
Oh, we make it to the playoff. I made it
to the playoffs. Our team made it to the
playoffs. No, I wanted it to be a moment
that like we could all share. So, like
when she thinks about us getting
engaged, it's in front of everybody,
right? It's in front of all the people
that support us, support the team. Um,
that's our moment now. And it's the fans
moment, too. So many people were a part
of that that like it's everybody's
moment now. So, like,
>> I'm blessed, brother.
>> I'm blessed, man. I I uh,
>> you know, I have no complaints. I have
zero complaints with my life and and and
the things that I've went through. And
truthfully, man, like if I had to go
through it again, I'd do it two times
over.
>> Wow.
>> You know, as crazy as that may sound,
>> but uh
pain breeds passion, brother,
>> and and it gives you a different aspect
on life
>> just in general, man. Like, so I'm uh
gratitude, brother. A lot of gratitude.
>> Amen, bro. And that's because you
weathered that storm. You're able to
have this gratitude and sit here today
because you weathered it. A lot of
people fold. A lot of people give up and
quit, brother. And you did not, man. So,
I'm just so happy for you, bro. All
these blessings coming, man. I'm telling
you, there's nothing better than being a
husband and having a wife, man. It just
it unlocked something different. And you
already done unlocked a lot. So, I can't
even imagine what's next for you, man.
>> Man, I mean, listen, me and you go by
the good word,
>> man.
>> And in the word, it says a man that find
a wife, find a good thing, right?
>> Find a great thing.
>> You know what I'm saying? So, hey, man,
the word tell me it's good, then it's
good. It's good. You see the proofs in
the poison right now.
>> Proof is in the pudding, brother. That I
that the word batting a thousand. It
ain't missed yet.
>> Amen.
>> You know, so I uh I'm just thankful,
man, to have somebody that uh God made
just for me. You know what I'm saying?
And uh I'm excited to share that bond
for uh till they put me six feet.
Brother,
>> look at you smiling and cheesy. Talking
about your lady, man. No, we talking
about the good word. And somebody that I
just found out will be sharing the good
word with you and your wife at your
wedding day
>> is your boy man Tres way. The the
world's favorite punter.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Did you ask him to do that? What goes
into that conversation cuz we know how
close you guys are. What goes into that,
man?
>> Yeah, man. Like Tres Tres changed my
life. A lot of people don't know it, but
uh he stood on the table for me when I
uh was on the P squad.
>> He changed the trajectory of my career.
Um,
>> so I the love I have for him will
forever be, you know, set in stone
because he didn't have to do that.
>> Yeah.
>> Um, but outside of that, right, like
that's family. Like his kids, my nephews
and nieces and like I'm Uncle Revo and I
love them, right? Um, and so why not
have him a part of the biggest day of my
life? He's been a part of a few of them.
>> Yeah.
>> He's changed my life.
He was the happiest person for me when I
became a pro bowler
>> for sure.
>> Um and so like I wanted him to be a part
of that. I wanted him to be included in
that because he is a big part of our
lives. Like he's taught me so much about
not only the football side of it, but
just like how to be a good man, how to
be a good husband, how to be a good
leader, how to be a good leader of the
home, what that looks like. I get to see
it from him with his family. And so like
Yeah, man. what I I couldn't think of
anybody else. So, we asked him and uh he
was ecstatic about it and and he was
just overjoyed. He's been texting us in
the group chat this week trying to
figure out the details. But, um
>> I'm just happy to have that day with my
guy.
>> Man, I think that's been one of my
favorite parts about being here is
watching y'all's relationship. Watching
him get the Pro Bowl and you being the
happiest person. We got family and kids
there and you smiling ear to ear, man.
watching the how you guys show up for
each other and just the love y'all have
for each other as brothers. Man, we me
and him talked about he was on the show
as well. Last question for you, man. Who
you think going to cry first? You or
Tress?
>> I got to say, Tres, I ain't going to
lie, cuz granted I'm going to see her
first cuz we doing first look.
>> Oh, are you guys going to do a first
look?
>> First look. Yeah, we trying to get the
pictures out early. We trying to have a
good time
before get lit.
>> You know what I'm saying? So,
I think once he sees all of us there,
like I think it's going to hit him for
sure. Yeah.
>> Yeah. And they Yeah, they did something.
I don't know what exactly, but I know
they did some type of tribute to my mom,
something,
>> man.
>> So, yeah. I I know I'm going to cry. I
don't know when, but I know I'm going to
cry, but I know Trust Trust going to cry
for sure.
>> Oh, dog, man. I mean, bro, I I cannot
imagine how proud of you, your mother
is, man, watching you do all of these
things and just just be a man, right?
Like, because it's one thing doing this
things we do on the field and making
this money and stuff like that, but
>> it takes something to be a great man, a
God-fearing man, and you did all of
that, brother. So, salute to you, man.
So happy for you. Last thing I'm going
to ask of you, brother, because you are
a fan favorite before you become a
married man looking at camera right
there. That's your ISO cam. And give a
message to the best fans in the NFL on
why you're excited to be back.
>> Man, I'm excited to be back with you
guys because you guys are a part of me
just as much as I'm a part of you. You
guys have weathered every storm with me.
You've been there. You supported me.
We've laughed, cried, had good days, had
bad days. We've had real life
experiences together. Um, and so you
guys show up for me. So, I'm just
excited to get to continue to show up
for y'all every Sunday and lay it all on
the line for y'all because y'all are a
huge part of why I'm here today. Um, the
words that you've given me over the
years, the encouragement, um, y'all
second to none. Uh, from the bottom of
my heart and my soon tobe family's
heart, I really, really appreciate you
guys. And thank you.
>> Oh, Pro Revo. My guy about to be a
married man. My boy got the bag running
it back for another year in the year
gold. Congrats on everything, brother.
Thank you, brother.
>> Command is family. This is Free Fridays
with our guy, our brother, our family,
Jeremy Reeves. And again, bro, congrats
on all the blessings you got headed your
way. You deserve it, bro.
>> Thank you, brother. Yes sir.